<resources>
    <string name="app_name">List</string>
    <string name="text1">$28.00</string>
    <string name="text">Clothing Item Name</string>
    <string name="TextView">Marigold is a very beautiful flower.</string>
    <string-array name="clothing">
        <item>Cross-back training tank</item>
        <item>Stretchy dance pant</item>
        <item>Ultra-soft tank top</item>
        <item>V-neck t-shirt</item>
        <item>V-neck sweater</item>
        <item>Polo shirt</item>
        <item>Skater graphic t-shirt</item>
        <item>Thermal fleece jacket</item>
        <item>V-neck pullover</item>
        <item>Grunge skater jeans</item>
        <item>Thermal vest</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="instructions">Calendula officinalis is a short-lived aromatic herbaceous
        perennial, growing to 80 cm (31 in) tall, with sparsely branched lax or erect stems.
        The leaves are oblong-lanceolate, 5–17 cm (2–7 in) long, hairy on both sides,
        and with margins entire or occasionally waved or weakly toothed.
        The inflorescences are yellow, comprising a thick capitulum or
        flowerhead 4–7 cm diameter surrounded by two rows of hairy bracts;
        in the wild plant they have a single ring of ray florets surrounding
        the central disc florets. The disc florets are tubular and hermaphrodite,
        and generally of a more intense orange-yellow colour than the female, tridentate,
        peripheral ray florets. The flowers may appear all year long where conditions are suitable.
        The fruit is a thorny curved achene. Calendula officinalis is a short-lived aromatic
        herbaceous perennial, growing to 80 cm (31 in) tall, with sparsely branched lax or erect
        stems. The leaves are oblong-lanceolate, 5–17 cm (2–7 in) long, hairy on both sides,
        and with margins entire or occasionally waved or weakly toothed.
        The inflorescences are yellow, comprising a thick capitulum or flowerhead 4–7 cm
        diameter surrounded by two rows of hairy bracts; in the wild plant they have a single
        ring of ray florets surrounding the central disc florets. The disc florets are tubular
        and hermaphrodite, and generally of a more intense orange-yellow colour than the female,
        tridentate, peripheral ray florets. The flowers may appear all year long where conditions
        are suitable. The fruit is a thorny curved achene.
    </string>
    <string name="my_detail_activity">MyDetailActivity</string>
</resources>
